[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bruce Willis claimed this actor helped him get over his divorce with Demi Moore in 2000.", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Ashton Kutcher", "Mel Gibson", "Denzel Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is Babys real name in Dirty Dancing (1987).", "correct_answer": "Frances", "incorrect_answers": ["Barbara", "Susan", "Jennifer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did the Black Mamba snake get its name?", "correct_answer": "Because its mouth is black", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of its color", "Because its eggs are black", "Because its venom is black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is said that Johnny Crawford used to take his horse with him on personal tours.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the modern safety pin created?", "correct_answer": "United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "France", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Uranus was renamed Urectum in what animated TV Series?", "correct_answer": "Futurama", "incorrect_answers": ["The Simpsons", "The Family Guy", "American Dad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The disastrous 2005 Atlantic hurricane season broke the 1933 record of 21 named storms.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following were an old-time radio duo?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Benny and Dennis Day", "George Burns and Gracie Allen", "Jack Benny and Mary Livingston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term arthro is of Greek origin. It refers to which part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Joint", "incorrect_answers": ["Head", "Skin", "Bone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio was not the first choice for the role of Jack in the movie Titanic.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Mediterranean islands belongs to Croatia and is home of the endangered Griffon Vulture?", "correct_answer": "Cres", "incorrect_answers": ["Filfla", "Procida", "Gorgona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This award is the oldest and most prominent film award, given annually for Hindi films in India.", "correct_answer": "The Filmfare Award", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mombay Gold Award", "The Diamond Star Award", "The Golden Lotus Award"]}]